Ron. Ron Ron. Ron
off.
During. Your.
Off. During
off. And bomb.
Bomb bomb during. The.
War. A way or
the.
Door.
Hard.
In.
The when you
where in the Air
France. Crash. General
Zod.
On another
homicide the Enron the
designer.
To
a whole I. Need.
Never mind and this is not the end
is sitting room Secretary man
a good. Adriana
. I say just want to listen and watch yet
another social life in the Army and one who
knows too much can very easily be sent
back to the Army and I'm not afraid and
then. One might never see the Aryans again
you know that for this position you
want to come to America didn't you.
You're terrified aren't you you're trembling
to stop it please Barry how are you
going to stab the sort of Peter you're
forgiving yourself you're fighting about
you're trying to hide but you can't
it's becoming more apparent every day.
The book came in last night he was out all
night and he got something home with him
and they. Were off to write up the.
Matter with you you're not even resting
I forgot why we're here you're not
interested in your work anymore you're
not interested me was you think about
business which he said was
a tough thing to do with it all I'm
interested in the news because I've got
a good show for her but
you're still in love with her
now Ray don't you see where you're heading
you want the same fate as his first wife
a suicide. Driver talked with one if I'm
truly after another is doing the same
thing to you the stuff we believe about
we can't you see I love you. Yes you well
I'll stand by the woman I loved all the
pieces I can't stand much more US. Some day
I'm going to kill it paying out.
Money my dear. PONY have
you paid the gas less for
just just making use to Joe's idea Jenny
I want to show I'm something and that's
why I don't want to be
in the city was giving
a lecture I told the secretary. I'd like
to invite Mr Wong to the Chinese detected
for your information is probably one of the
five families living authorities on H.
And art and literature
and they are he is also
a graduate of Heidelberg
in Oxford need that
Lorraine hourlong is this
marking going to continue
a lot Peter would you ask
Michael sleazy by practicing
a little later television or you said yes.
It was your idea that we bring stalking
up to America you said he was wasting his
marvellous talent didn't you yes well enough
to keep up with his practicing is that
right IMO generalists I was just so he
could face desires on you that's not true
I'm not blind he has
a great attraction for women
hasn't he I hadn't noticed no no
and I don't like your insinuation you know
I'm only interested in his voice so then
fuck my char interesting young parents and
be here in saying that he was trying to
do to me Want to get accomplished
something I'm starting up well mistreated
sensorimotor way in case you're worrying
about my absence last night I was
receiving the I have the daughter of the
most grand but you didn't bring the
jewel into this house right not
will be murdered. No there's still
a valid. What would happen to the
dilemma of China and Oriental
superstition is that
a terror the president wrong told you and
they said the Emperor was very jealous of
his wife when
a very place the gem. Well
. I'm afraid I mean. I
should have learned to have.
Not read it. Too long my
wife nice. You could come.
This is. Japanese I happened.
To remember that night.
Reading cap. Stuff and.
Please encourage the my
the other be over in
a corner with the entire
night. I musta missed.
You never met one before. Never met.
And
a very good friend. Matched
. Yes.
This connection. Haps
now that I found this.
The dog from the movie recognizes course
the most beautiful thing in
the world exclusive to God
that he dangerous because the Chinese
government know it's in this country I don't
think so they're searching for this missing
from the museum after the looting of
man the king I suppose you realize
your life may be in danger my
life is in danger
printed this. The day before I obtain
possession of the stone the day before that's
the real reason I was so anxious to have
you come yet and have you consulted the
police no one why don't you consult
a trained Jack as you know he's
a noted criminologists Edirne is in and
out of here all the time actively one of
the household I prefer to
consult someone who has
a terror perspective that's
why I sent for you. Keep this
side arriving the day before
and you suspect no one.
I have made
a state which is contained in the sample
is to be opened of anything should happen
to me the name of the person
I suspect is in here.
Missy Well you know very well saying.
Absolutely trustworthy is devoted to me
for Mrs Eddy was going to play some sort
of game downstairs I think it's called
indications now the you know you act
on some song the song playoff picture.
In England we used to call them
now that. I've been to assist.
Ladies and gentlemen we're
going to play indication.
We left out of the title one
a song well known song to
a book mystery. And
a movie an extremely popular movie I assure
you and they'll be up all of our very
best champagne for that very clever
person will get to each one first.
My first appearance as a performer
or Never mind the lack of
a very good. As Brandon been showing you
some of the treasure trove we brought back
from China to show you the beautiful
manuscript he has with the legend No I didn't
know you. Well but I don't oh you're playing
the part of your rights lover my life
lover and that's
a novel twist but what happens. He finds
you two together and. You know I
think you've got something there I
don't know why do I say anything
oh yes the lines let's go I love.
I am and that's. The last
that you saw that I did.
What the owners that are.
Well well what is it. Oh man on the
go no no no no come on now try
again oh this is easy come on sailing
sailing over the ocean way you get it wrong
someone else. Oh I know
the thought of boatman.
This is Gordon was the
first battle of Shaft
a good chap it. Just
does not know what it. Oh the speech oh
what I'm in the midst of want to know.
And now number two the mystery
no less this and then your
host and hostess will play the leading
roles in this one I'll pay begins on the
stock of the night.
But.
You shouldn't have come
why I had to see you
Valerie I love you less
than I love you Joan
you must and my husband may be
a week your husband is away. What
are you doing in my wife's arms I mean
what's my wife doing in your arms we've been
in love with each other for months and
months and months it will be fun to let you
live and suffer but as for him die like
a dog. Now
can he turn
a triangle not this time. Not another. God
come but just thinking caps on.
Then don't tell no tales. Not even
well I've got it let's play Murder. That.
I call on the eminent criminologist
protested Jenny Oh well.
I should say it's. What you know.
I had the last thought when you
make an effort Mr Watt Oh. I would
suggest. That midnight.
Going to get your fiance and
a bottle of soda pop with
a professor. Of
law and you. Buy
a first. Book for him
particularly that of our friend.
Even the president get up and take
a pot Rand and it's all over
brand.
His first.
Let me I'll take it to
a room then I'll call the police. I'm
afraid there has been
a gun fortunate accident your
post. Please do not disturb
and
I would like to have
a but. Please with
the telephone it's been on
the table for that but I get
a mistress the last one. Who
suggested this particular place.
I did wrong I skipped out Oh and
I was to play the. Why didn't you.
They needed me for another sketch so
I suggested he said who loaded
the gun and which he loaded with
black so I sat right here watched it
and watch the god damn it out of your
possession after it was loaded. I don't
think so I've ever had loaded an exam with
them I just put it let's not.
I want to.
WHAT HAPPENED LAST up
that way for the choir.
One I don't expect to find you here I
expected you but not so sue somebody fun is
about twenty minutes ago said it was
a homicide who from did they say. Why
is it important twenty minutes ago the
victim was still alive learn what
goes on here but I'd hoped it was an
accident now I wonder
why this building stops Yes. Now.
All right well the first part is he was
sick and Mr and Mrs Edwards were given to
the plate which this young man was
supposed to shoot it was with this gun
these are blanks Yes yes sure it's me
that you saw Edwards load the god himself
with those blacks and so far as he knows
the governor's not been out of his
possession but some one time but
with the gun but the man is dead
was anybody else with you when this
gun was loaded I was there to handle
a gun no they were
about to start this thing at the beginning
Riley's people having his gun was fired
yes we would all know.
What kept us all know.
And we all thought it was just an amusing
play until Mrs Edwards told I was going
to get up and he didn't. Wear them as Edward
he was taken to her room by Professor
damage here as he too was
a guest of the party one of the gathering
of the clan we three of were together for
. Let's talk and I said was it
a Stick around ladies and gentlemen go
home leave your name and address of the
officer at the top. Of line about
here and give me your name
make
a more comfortable. FOR
THE STREET HOW DO YOU GET here somebody
from this side as I can gather before the
shooting occurred and they sing like to
talk to Mrs Edwards Oh please don't don't
disturb if she's hot out of the night
actually prostrate I'm sure she'll think this
maybe you can help each
other. What's this.
Well all we have to do is actually find
out whether that young secretary No that
was
a real bullet might get money for that it's
not quite as simple as that there is somebody
curious angles in this case it's important
to get the report from the ballistics
Department why I just want to be sure that
the bullet in it with the body really
came from Houghton's gun well as usual
routine down early in the morning I will
it's all very puzzling it hasn't always
seemed to be on the best of terms
saying. It's true isn't it Mr Gray
but Mr Harrison we're good friends
big front yesterday you mean they had
a fist fight no big talk loud
Have you any idea what the
choir was about not. Tell
a policeman the brain has
an eye like plate and.
Where you're going. I'm going to miss that
restaurant oh I want to see you in fact
Mr Hanson all pleased I cannot.
So that Mr Harrison you had acquired
yesterday with a Briggs did you know that is
a true yes what you call about I
can tell you you mean you refuse
yet I'll have to hold you as
a material witness which is the same
as being under arrest and practically.
Night in jail of some in this town and I
hope it will be solved as easily that I
think of real that bird myself if I don't
get anywhere I'll turn the motor the two
foremost criminologists
on the Pacific coast.
You don't believe it was an accident do
you will suffer I've no reason to suspect
otherwise I have
a very definite reason for suspecting
foul play. I didn't mention it
but it would showed me
a sealed letter in his safe which was to
be opened in case of his death by violence
you mean to say he hadn't dissipated in
the temple the middle his life and he
suspected so long of course that's what's
in the letter though of course that
reason
a bit jealous of Valerie the singer of
the struggle herbalism an example Cisco
that are
a hundred million murdered how do
you propose to open the safe that
may not be so easy
a matter. I had opened.
And the letters gone. I have
a daughter of them all I
feel the daughter of them
too many of the true dynasty Yes but
action the Imperial collection in nineteen
No it was lost in the looting of neck
somehow or other Edward Cup as Ephron he
showed it to me earlier this
evening and I think first. Some.
That friends have
a taste for that sort of thing. Thank
presumably the person who stole the I took.
With just
a little lease I know means we'd better
not give the freight street too much to
think about what no. I think you
know I better stay the night yet
good. Let's have
a look around before returning. Nothing
at all seeing. You
a problem late she like constant we
can not look see by bright lights.
I want you to go to the house of the Seven
Brothers on Broad Street talk to some
yet asking who in Chinatown sells
this kind of paper and to whom
they find paper it's not the ordinary
paper made from straw it's from the rice
paper tree it may have come from home
province this may not be easy to do the best
you can
this is a microphone a graph
of the sailboat taken from
a bridge body. An outsider to
show up with their eyes and.
In their helmets. They don't though
it was never Cider House and
I didn't think it was noticed test building
has none of the peculiar markings at
the base of this could.
These be curio markings
could they have been caused by
a silencer Yes perhaps that's what happened
in the ads in case you remember Janice
I had
a hunch it turned out this way when I got
the coroner's report by the way to just
say that the bullet traveled in a
downward direction that it was fired from
a height Yeah how do you know
but I found this last night
balcony overlooking state I said
thirty eight that's the right caliber
then it was deliberate murder. And that's
not all because like I said with the
Chinese waiting on my
outer office what I find
a lot of the scenes that average changed
as well and Carl's lake was on the way to
Edwards' house this morning to
get a signature. Got a lot of
a an A This is Mr while we're helping the
police in the investigation Mister I want
you Bill guys like it's been definitely
proven that your client was not killed with
a bullet that came from Harrison's gun
this is murder I'm not entirely surprised
but you remember that there was something
wrong in that house and atmosphere of
approaching Do I felt it ever since Mr
Edwards returned from his recent trip to
China just out of the terms of the no will
different from the old ones Ordinarily
I'd consider this information is
confidential but Mr Edwards altered his will
practically eliminating this it had words
from every benefit possible disinherited
Mrs Edwards practically as much as was
possible how about seeing the back just to
what extent was he benefit but
the new Will what he did with
a bridge for years he had the largest legacy
of all I wonder how much that Chinaman
really now there's ways that
are dark and tricks that of
a you know what I mean wrong. I think the
sooner we get out that was house and
question everybody the better and I
think you should know that Edwards left
a letter needs to be opened in the event
of the day he did I mean Jenny and I go
for it last night it was God How do you
know Edwards didn't take themselves but
showed it to me just before we went
downstairs and as you know he never came up
again and I think we better get out there
right now of course you realize that
there's definitely eliminate junk How does
our lease but I'm going to take along
for further questioning might be useful.
What is it saying please don't step they
want to see me want to see everybody
Peter Galbraith teleplays
will both be down shortly.
They released you yes they found that the
bullet that killed your husband wasn't
fired from my gun I knew you couldn't
have done it well there waiting.
In other words no one went
up that stairway outside
a struggle that's right when the
play rule on some other great.
Because of how are you Mrs
Edwards is that please Mrs
Edwards as much it's been definitely
established that your husband was murdered it
opens up a new line of
investigation if you want
a personal suspicions no
there's no one I was just
happy with the idea while your husband
cooperate with the secretary Mrs Edwards I
wasn't aware they had called I think I can
explain that possibly Harrison literally
objected to the terms
a new will which disinherited Mrs Edwards'
mom so that's why your quarrel and
yet unlike the idea of in changing
the world you know that you know
you know one thing about
it. And you Mrs Edwards No
but I'm not surprised
seems to me that it's
a pretty good motive for murder.
Get rid of that man before he had
a chance to sign and that's.
If you don't mind sergeant I'd like to
return to my office thanks for coming one
moment please how did you feel about
changing that this will naturally I was and
they are they were just
a lovely and charming lady I thought Edwards
was insane and I didn't hesitate to
tell him so I quarreled with him as
a bit silly as anyone in fact I told him
to get someone else to look at real legal
affairs I didn't see what party last night
I was invited but the last moment I
decided not to come I took a ride
in my car alone and you live only
a few doors from here well yes why I mean
we can get in touch with the reason we
need yes and the thank you that
we use st I'd have
a few officers on duty tonight I think
you're right Professor Jenny and I
have decided to spend the night.
Much smoke.
This felicitous of pig. Congealed
the trees on the mountaintop
closures of the way yes the
forgery could be. The aboriginal
stolen from Temple that's just.
Blown bridges and God to destroy
you know something don't you but you
hold your tongue more languages than
one my friend.
And we still treat you wouldn't come it
wasn't so we must be very careful so
worried about you still Soon
it will be OK I hope so.
Because what they need to do of course but
I haven't got. You were up staying there
I mean you could upstairs are you lying
you mustn't say such things you have no
reason to doubt we have and I was with
you can married as soon as you reached
America that was three months ago but I
explained to you that it would be getting
them to my God you know very
well your career was only
a blind but that unity and I stand
a great disability this country all can
go out together but I was just going to
have
a little dig fall I do enjoy
it why not look at me again to
understand you took the stone and you're
trying to hold out on me you are crazy not
as crazy as you think and I'd advise you
to be careful are you threatening me I
found the letter in the state that you are
not what that letter that Edwards wrote
naming the one suspected boy that would
you like to know what are you going to do
with them to spoil your plans and everyone
else is in that house I want to give it
to the police and tell them that you
stole it in the sake don't be sick
all right then and then after
a while you I abruptly
wait to find that out.
While you come in from door
to go meet him either.
A judge must compress the Senate.
They're going to let. Now
anything that they don't open the
someone in the House who can tell them
that they can only welcome our next count
noses and find out now.
What's wrong and allow our mind open with
all that room I think we've got to take
a look Janet Yellen that doesn't
around now doesn't go again everybody.
I don't understand that's
a tall but I don't Mr X.
Should have to force an entrance
into the house of Mrs X. Or Miss X.
.
What happened in
a strange house the old. Money to
charity went out to everybody here.
Where this way.
This.
Place is all upset because
it's being searched
they are going to call street. They're
going to run away right all right let's
clear
a room. Out in the street. Oh
I was just having
a drink to join us I think
I guess that one. Got. One
to join us but
a drink. That. I would like. Take
another five dollar.
Have you found something wrong I'm going
to the letter but you had with Mr needs so
that no letter was deprived in the
wastepaper basket in his bedroom
I've always assumed that are
a still the letter from the shakes some
heart of it fell into green eyes have it so
that she knew they were dead and
she in turn was killed herself.
When was the literal as the lesson. We'd
all feel safer if we knew but in any event
whether has it or find it later it's
obviously. A Don't you think so again. Your
whole friends think.
I'm slightly sore about the whole thing
I take every possible precaution what
happens when he gets in the house and kills
that girl right under our very nose and
the newspapers get ahold of this I'll tell
the police that I'm going to park I've
got
a strict instructions for every door and
women that have to be locked and I want to
get off them I was going through some of
their good Chinese manuscripts in the dead
I'd smoked a good deal soon came in
and opened the window when I was
a girl that lets you forget all your dead
and sure you didn't arrange to lay that
all over some one room full of bad air in
the open window only forget to close it
does anybody know what this girl is doing
Ali she go outside she coming from dark
Misener that's seventh in the habit of
coming in to the front door that's what I
ask her whether she don't want
to so she go meet him one
that she yes she was on her way to mail
a letter when I met just an accident and I
know it was prearranged she wants to see
me but if you talk about
a purely personal matter. Discussing
personal matters and the SO. I WANT TO KNOW
THIS ago we were friends and just
friends when she learned that coming to
the states with Mrs Edwards she persuaded
her to take that offer which she made in
China with
a dancer in the cafe in the fog and said
that most members know that her maid was
your sweetheart. But what
has that. Might have
a lot to do with. What was the personal
matter you were discussing last night she
was insisting that I was getting that
it and if you're if you're. She was
threatening to cause
a terrific scandal. Did you believe that
you'd actually do this thing. And I told
her so then what happened she got
very angry and she left. You to mail
a letter to stop and yes did she mailed
the letter I don't know do you happen to
know to whom the letter was addressed No I
haven't seen the address how do you get
back in the house through a French
window I elected. Sure you didn't climb
a ladder and get back in the house that
way quite sure. I mean I go to your rooms
that is all except Mr stroganoff
is telling the truth the next step is to
find out how much you forgot to tell us
you really think you know something and I
know something whoever killed Edwards and
that girl is on these premises right now
I'm quite sure that why somebody took
a shot at
a shot when we learned in the evening I
was outside I was trying to make the cost
of the print the base of that we never
shot cost us the science and that's why we
didn't hear the shock killed. But you
shouldn't take those chances one who.
The more I think of it the more I think
he knows more than he's telling us you
think you killed his sweetheart or shut
up when she threaten to talk I think
I'll take struggling after they had
caught us getting ready George.
You know he claims that they are
saying it all right and they can sing.
I don't.
Know whether it was or no. But.
You say I came into the French one is that's
correct why did you go upstairs to my
own and how do you account for the fact
that the policeman on duty in the hallway
didn't see about the stairs I went up the
back stairs to talk to the maid Yes Just
say no I knocked at the door and there was
no answer then why did you go to my room
and to bed.
So when you say paper block from China
by calmly company this out paper with
a few people here lives
up there who buys them.
I saw that zero six six one. Yes
Mr well about the letter.
She shipped.
I had number. Just shipped.
She. Shipped its.
Straight house. Yeah right here. Now I
was speaking on the freight something's
happened at the advertise I'll be in front
of your house with
a squad drawn ten minutes come on down. I
want to. Bring in an.
I like I like somebody hit him on the head
literally and see what you can find on
the handler.
You say you were talking to him on the phone
if you hear any other voices No I just
heard
a commotion I want my to be interested in
performing body so I called you immediately
. John is right the sound of anyone down
hit your body out there check the stairs
look around the grounds. And if you read
a lot of the work is that he lives in
a nice. State.
Street. But usually says what happened how
they killed him now he's only knocked
out well I wanted only. Where he has really
been on the ground walking in the Rose
Garden I said to the battery go out
and get some fresh air we took
a house along with us because my suggestion
but when this happened we haven't been
out of the House because in our whole much
less than half an hour that's right yes
and we've been together all the time well
yes of course and that's one thing I'm
sure of stroganoff didn't do this
because he's been with me the letter
that's the one thing I got out of struggle
that letter was intended for you yes it
was single speaking of if any of
us fact. PLEASE PLEASE PLEASE
IT'S A letter written by your late husband
containing the name of the person he
suspected to be opened after his
death in the event of foul play
then he didn't know evidently at the
assailant but seeing had the letter with
a severed Sunny Boy it's not necessary I
dropped the seeing earlier than today. The
letter is in the nail it
will be in my hands in
a very few hours. Expect
versus I'm expecting
a visitor to all. Of the dogs that
made any one of the cards. Why
Good evening this is the letter have
you received. Have you opened this
allow me to offer you some. As if
you did my husband suspect you
suspected the one who hated my
husband had many enemies is it
possible that that could
include young Harrison. No no.
Mr while you have asked then the real
reason of the our being here is that your
afraid his name might be in your
husband's letter is that it. Who I had
assumed you were just speaking of you
Well Peter why did you come here
for the same reason you did is it possible
you both have an identical interest in
the contents of this letter.
The stuff too long and I told you
it would make anyone who came
to. Excuse me
a moment it's hard to be so late
but I mistook it up he wanted to know where
you live so I brought him along. About
Paris I came to ask you Mr Wrong
to open that letter until I have
a chance to tell you that your name is not
Stroger not the better of it if you knew
the dead wood to the pain perception of the
eye of the daughter of the moon if you
were in the dream no one has confidence
and came to America with him to get the
snow even if you had to kill it. You have
to mean too much with the wrong that
remains to be seen in the
meantime. Please because.
I couldn't help thinking what you said
about my living so near the Edwards now if
you think for one moment that I had anything
to do with this. Why Mrs Edwards if
you contemplate making
a statement of any so I must insist as
your attorney if you're first in something
surely you don't think Mrs Edwards
might incriminate herself Now I
submit that we are all here for one purpose
to identify the murderer of Brandon it
. This letter stolen from his safe and
subsequently mailed to me contains the
name of the suspect the I think the letter
my hope and I'm afraid is not quite as
easy as that as we all know it but had
a great many enemies and would be
grossly unfair to kind of suspicion on
a possibly innocent person until we have
sifted all the facts but what are your
deductions to this point Edwards could have
been murdered for two widely different
first and most obvious one of course is the
theft of the eye of the dollar move my
first thought was possibly from. Friends
of China struck to recover what
was rightfully their But
my countrymen here or in
a position to know assure me that that
is not true so they come to miss the
stroganoff whose sole purpose in coming
to America was to steal the stuff
but Mr Wong how possibly could the mother
of god help me to gain possession of this
stall which was locked
in the safe in and then
a different part of the house my dear Mr
stroke about we have arrived at exactly
the same conclusion so I'm afraid we
must discard the theory of the stole
altogether. When you don't think the world
is going to obtain possession of the
stone that person of the past about what
you remember of course treat uncover the
fact that the will was changed and he was
first killed before he signed it there we
come to the second perhaps the stronger
motive in that event who would be the
interested party of course
with Mrs Edwards and
young habits and devotion to his employer's
wife was obvious but the report of the
department of ballastic spruce that the
bullet was not far from how this one's gun
and Mrs Edwards was standing alongside
of her husband at the moment that the
shoppers fired from the balcony overlooking
steak so could they have had an
accomplice Karslake has admitted
to climbing violently with Edwards
over the terms of the new will but then
again st investigation corroborate his
story that he did go to the Dr that night
and was nowhere near the house at the
time well I confess
that I am completely at
a loss and it's no small cost to my
professional pride I shall have to
seek the solution in this letter unless
you will come to my rescue Janet and tell
me why you killed Edward
right here what I'm
sure you're not serious I'm sorry Janet I
was never more serious in my life but my
deal you made so many mistakes stakes
the fact that the jury misled me for
a while but why the warning. For the very
paper on which it was written the type of
rice paper ready found in this country was
easily traced to your university where
it's used in the repairing
of ancient manuscripts here
there was
a mistake then you went out of your way
to draw my attention to the manuscript
where an obvious forgery which you had
encouraged Edwards to buy so I feel sure you
went is free then came the question of
motive. When I discovered that Edwards first
wife was your sister and you
had watched him drive her to
a suicide to grave I was certain that you
had every reason to hate Yes that's true
he drove my sister Mary to her death I
was short of it he knew of my conviction
because I want him at the time of his
marriage to Valerie back with my great state
you know of course Valerie married him to
save her father from going to prison for
over three years I stood quietly by and
watched him pursuing the same tactics using
the same insidious true it is against
her that he was against my sister
when I heard he was going to disinherit
her then I made up my mind to
remove him. The read.
The autopsy showed she
died of poison smoke inhaled it. I Can't
Believe me my dear Well I would have saved
her if I called her death is
the one thing in all this on
a business that I regret
no Janet. Both say.
I trace the source of that
poison but I can't find
a man that brought it here xian that Jenny
by well congratulations I'm sorry.
Charlie go St It's getting
late and I haven't slept for
a week kind
of breaks up
a nice combination doesn't it all
right folks that's all good now
they're wrong the letter he S.
Has in the middle of.
It's blank paper when I
was in rather an embarrassing position when
the real letter mailed by saying failed
to arrive about that served it's. How did
you tell you Jenny under that bridge I
happen to remember when the
lights went out he left me for
a few more I then found he'd had time to
get to the balcony and back. When I was
five and later on in the garden I got an
old squeak with but the silence it wasn't
difficult to put the two together
providing they could find
a motive for Janet which I unfortunately
we did but once again St I
must say that back to your valuable
assistance I couldn't have solved the case
thanks one I'll put that in the
report Good night good night
messenger just bring
them out it is important
not to. Get some fresh tea
though I don't want anybody
to know if you are going on
a very important evidence for me yes
taking back to China something that
belongs.